Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - A-D
        - Del Tha Funkee Homosapien - Sleepin' on my couch; Ahonetwo, ahonetwo, 1991; SR-8187; Del Tha Funkee Homosapien (Box 25)
          Catalog # 0-66527; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-66527-A-1-
        - Delegation - Delegation II, 1981; SR-8188; Delegation (Box 25)
          Catalog # SRM-1-4004; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-4004-AS-PW
        - Delfonics - The Delfonics, 1970; SR-8189; Delfonics (Box 25)
          Catalog # PG-1153; A-side Matrix # S-35440 PG1153
          Philly Groove Records
        - Delfonics - Tell me this is a dream, 1972; SR-8190; Delfonics (Box 25)
          Catalog # SW-94428; A-side Matrix # SW1 94428 R1
        - Delgado, Junior - Raggamuffin year, 1986; SR-8191; Delgado, Junior (Box 25)
          Catalog # MLPS 9803; A-side Matrix # A- MLPS-9803-A
          Mango
        - Delinquent Habits - Delinquent habits (disc one), 1996; SR-8173; Delinquent Habits (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-7184. Double album.
          Catalog # 07863-66929-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-66929-1 A
          Loud Records
        - Delinquent Habits - Delinquent habits (disc two), 1996; SR-8174; Delinquent Habits (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-7183. Double album.
          Catalog # 07863-66929-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-66929-1 C
        - Delt, Kennie - Funky musak, 1979; SR-8192; Delt, Kennie (Box 25)
          Catalog # MK-88; A-side Matrix # MK-88 B-CTI IT
        - Demian, Max - The call of the wild, 1980; SR-8176; Demian, Max (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8177. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # AFL1-3525; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3525 A-S
        - Demian, Max - The call of the wild, 1980; SR-8177; Demian, Max (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8176. Multiple copies.
        - Democrates D - La voie du peuple (disc one), 1995; SR-8178; Democrates D (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8179. Double album.
          Catalog # 121097; A-side Matrix # 121097 A DEMOCRATES D SIDE A MPO
          Wotre Music
        - Democrates D - La voie du peuple (disc two), 1995; SR-8179; Democrates D (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8178. Double album.
          Catalog # 121097; A-side Matrix # 121097 C DEMOCRATES D SIDE C MPO
        - Depeche Mode - Stripped (Highland mix), 1986; SR-8193; Depeche Mode (Box 25)
          Catalog # 12 BONG 10; A-side Matrix # 12 BONG 10 A1X
          Mute
        - Depeche Mode - See you, 1982; SR-8194; Depeche Mode (Box 25)
          Catalog # 0-29957; A-side Matrix # 1818 0 29957 0-29957-A B-16856-A Re 2
          Sire
        - Depeche Mode - Big muff; Photographic; Nodisco; Boys say go!, 1981; SR-8197; Depeche Mode (Box 25)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1025; A-side Matrix # ORO-A1-1025 SH2 B-16637 SH2
        - Depeche Mode - It's no good, 1997; SR-8198; Depeche Mode (Box 25)
          Catalog # PRO-A-8662-A; A-side Matrix # PRO-A8662-AS21
        - Depeche Mode - Mega mix part 1; Mega mix part 2, 1990; SR-8199; Depeche Mode; DPM (Box 25)
          Catalog # DPM 07; A-side Matrix # DPM-07-A
          ON-Usound
        - Deserters - Deserters, 1981; SR-8201; Deserters (Box 25)
          Catalog # ST-12164; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12164 F2
        - Desir - Oh Madiana; Zombi, 1983; SR-8204; Desir (Box 25)
          Catalog # 813 253-1; A-side Matrix # 161 8132531 A POLYGRAM
          Franck R. Records
          West Indies
        - Jonny Destry & Destiny - Girls, rock 'n roll & cars, 1980; SR-8205; Jonny Destry & Destiny (Box 25)
          Catalog # BXL1-7753; A-side Matrix # BXL-1-7753-11
        - Desvarieux, Jacob F. - Jacob F. Desvarieux & Georges Décimus, 1984; SR-8206; Desvarieux, Jacob F.; Décimus, Georges (Box 25)
          Catalog # GD 022; A-side Matrix # I GD 022 A
          GD Productions
        - Deutsch Amerikanische Freundschaft - Für immer, 1982; SR-8181; Deutsch Amerikanische Freundschaft (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8182. Different discs.
          Catalog # V2239; A-side Matrix # V-2239-A4
        - Deutsch Amerikanische Freundschaft - Für immer, 1982; SR-8182; Deutsch Amerikanische Freundschaft (Box 25)
          In same jacket as # SR-8181. Different discs.
          Catalog # 204.956; A-side Matrix # 204 956 A
        - Diabaté, Zani - Zani Diabaté et le Super Djata Band, 1985; SR-8207; Diabaté, Zani; Super Djata Band (Box 25)
          Catalog # MM 85-1001; A-side Matrix # MM 85-1001 A
          Milady Music
        - Gregg Diamond Bionic Boogie - Tiger tiger, 1979; SR-8208; Gregg Diamond Bionic Boogie; Diamond, Gregg; Bionic Boogie (Box 25)
          Catalog # PD-1-6237; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6237-AS-CP1
        - Dibango, Manu - Mboa, 1982; SR-8209; Dibango, Manu (Box 25)
          Catalog # AF 1983; A-side Matrix # AF 1983
          AfroVision Records
        - Tom Dickie & the Desires - Burnin' up, 1981; SR-21115; Tom Dickie & the Desires; Dickie, Tom (Box 25)
          Catalog # MK 171; A-side Matrix # MK-171-2-56331-PW
        - Difford & Tilbrook - Difford & Tilbrook, 1984; SR-21116; Difford & Tilbrook (Box 25)
          Catalog # SP-4985; A-side Matrix # SP-04985-A EUR-1
          A&M Records
        - Digital Underground - The "body-hat" syndrome (disc one), 1993; SR-8184; Digital Underground (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-8185. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # TB 1080; A-side Matrix # 1-1080 A
          Tommy Boy
        - Digital Underground - The "body-hat" syndrome (disc two), 1993; SR-8185; Digital Underground (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-8184. Double album. Promo
          Catalog # TB 1080; A-side Matrix # 1-1080 C
        - Digital Underground - Who got the gravy? (disc one), 1998; SR-8195; Digital Underground (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-8196. Double album.
          Catalog # INT-90261; A-side Matrix # INT2-90261-A INT2-90261
          Interscope Records
        - Digital Underground - Who got the gravy? (disc two), 1998; SR-8196; Digital Underground (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-8195. Double album.
          Catalog # INT-90261; A-side Matrix # INT2-90261-C 1
        - Digital Underground - Sons of the P, 1991; SR-21117; Digital Underground (Box 26)
          Catalog # TBLP 1045; A-side Matrix # TB-1045 A
        - Dillinger - Cokane in my brain, 1977; SR-21118; Dillinger (Box 26)
          Catalog # MS 10007; A-side Matrix # MS-1007-A-RE1
          Mango Records
        - Dillinger - Live at London, 1981; SR-21119; Dillinger; Eastwood, Clint (Box 26)
          Catalog # JSLP 0020; A-side Matrix # JSLP-0020-A-1
          Jamaica Sound
        - Di Meola, Al - Land of the midnight sun, 1976; SR-21120; Di Meola, Al (Box 26)
          Catalog # PC 34074; A-side Matrix # PAL-3407 4-1G
        - Dino - 24/7, 1989; SR-21121; Dino (Box 26)
          Catalog # BWAY4011; A-side Matrix # BWAY-4011-A
          4th & Broadway
        - Dinosaur - Kiss me again, 1978; SR-8202; Dinosaur (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-8203. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # PRO-A-771; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-1-771-KMI
        - Dinosaur - Kiss me again, 1978; SR-8203; Dinosaur (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-8202. Different discs.
          Catalog # SRD 1035; A-side Matrix # SRD-1035-WNY-1715-S-JWI
        - Direct Current - Everybody here must party, 1979; SR-21122; Direct Current (Box 26)
          Catalog # #59; A-side Matrix # STEREO 33 1/3 DHCO 59-A VIRTUE STUDIOS PHIL. PA.
          TEC Records
        - Divine Sounds - Changes; Do or die Bed Sty, 1984; SR-21123; Divine Sounds (Box 26)
          Catalog # D-229; A-side Matrix # D229A
          Specific Records
          Englewood, New Jersey
        - Divine Styler - Word power, 1989; SR-21124; Divine Styler; Scheme Team (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21125. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # E 45299; A-side Matrix # PAL-45299-1A G 1
          Rhyme $yndicate Records
        - Divine Styler - Word power, 1989; SR-21125; Divine Styler; Scheme Team (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21124. Multiple copies.
        - Dixie Cups - Chapel of love, 1964; SR-21126; Dixie Cups (Box 26)
          Catalog # RB 20-100; A-side Matrix # RB-20100A-1A
          Red Bird
        - DJ Baby Anne - Version 5.1, 2000; SR-21127; DJ Baby Anne (Box 26)
          Catalog # Zone 039; A-side Matrix # ZONE 039-A
          Zone Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - DJ Big Red - I'm a alcoholik!!!, 1997; SR-21128; DJ Big Red (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21129. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # BB-01; A-side Matrix # 9711V31-A
          Baltimore Breakbeat Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - DJ Big Red - I'm a alcoholik!!!, 1997; SR-21129; DJ Big Red (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21128. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Big Red - Weed on Friday, 1998; SR-21130; DJ Big Red (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21131. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # BB010; A-side Matrix # 9808X61-A
        - DJ Big Red - Weed on Friday, 1998; SR-21131; DJ Big Red (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21130. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Booman - Blow your whistle 1999, 1999; SR-21132; DJ Booman (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21133. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # RSPCLB-0001-VL; A-side Matrix # RSPCLB-0001-VL-A
          Respect Records
        - DJ Booman - Blow your whistle 1999, 1999; SR-21133; DJ Booman (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21132. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Booman - What! What!; Come on down, 1998; SR-21134; DJ Booman (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21135. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PKH-02; A-side Matrix # DR-20281M-A PKH-02A
          Phat Kidz Recordings
          Maryland
        - DJ Booman - What! What!; Come on down, 1998; SR-21135; DJ Booman (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21134. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Brandon Rauch - Super deejays, 2000; SR-21136; DJ Brandon Rauch; Wilson, Jon (Box 26)
          Catalog # NRA 001; A-side Matrix # 0001V17 A A+R SPGII
          National Rhythm Army Records
        - DJ Butta Loops - More hot butta beats & loops volume 6, 1998; SR-21137; DJ Butta Loops (Box 26)
          Catalog # BLP-6; A-side Matrix # BLP-6-A
          WW Records
        - DJ Cartman - Toolbox; Disco pulpo, 1999; SR-21138; DJ Cartman (Box 26)
          Catalog # grow! 18; A-side Matrix # MPO GROW!18 B2
          Grow!
        - DJ Creme - The reggaeton remix project, 2000; SR-21139; DJ Creme (Box 26)
          Catalog # CREME-1; A-side Matrix # CREME-1-A
          DJ Creme
        - DJ Cuca - DJ Cuca in the place, 1988; SR-21140; DJ Cuca (Box 26)
          Catalog # LP DN 097; A-side Matrix # DN 097 A LL 4 89
          TNT Records
          Brazil
        - DJ Czech - The general, 1999; SR-21141; DJ Czech (Box 26)
          Catalog # FFR 001; A-side Matrix # FF-01 A
          Futuristic Funk Records
          Vancouver, British Columbia
        - DJ Debbie D - Rock the beat, 2001; SR-21173; DJ Debbie D (Box 26)
          Catalog # DR002; A-side Matrix # DR-001-1-A PCMJR
          D-Style Records
        - DJ Debonair Samir - DJ Debonair Samir, 2000; SR-21142; DJ Debonair Samir (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21143. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # CTX-2; A-side Matrix # CTX 2 A
          Clubtrax Records
        - DJ Debonair Samir - DJ Debonair Samir, 2000; SR-21143; DJ Debonair Samir (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21142. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Dero - Supertango, 2003; SR-21144; DJ Dero; Mr. X (Box 26)
          Catalog # NF | DMD | 03 | 002; A-side Matrix # B377499 01 A1 HL
          Nextfire Recordings
        - DJ Djill - D'art2style Break, 2000; SR-21145; DJ Djill; Doze (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21146. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # BB 001; A-side Matrix # DFI 01-5 BB001 A
          DD
        - DJ Djill - D'art2style Break, 2000; SR-21146; DJ Djill; Doze (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21145. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Eclipse - Reach out, 2002; SR-21147; DJ Eclipse (Box 26)
          Catalog # BAS 012; A-side Matrix # BAS012-A
          Bad Ass Shit!
          Lantana, Florida
        - DJ Equalizer - Balls & knuckles vol. 2, 1995; SR-21148; DJ Equalizer; Sounds of Silence (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21149. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # ICR 016; A-side Matrix # ICR-016-DIS "A"
          Inner City Records Co.
        - DJ Equalizer - Balls & knuckles vol. 2, 1995; SR-21149; DJ Equalizer; Sounds of Silence (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21148. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Equalizer - The Sounds of Silence DJ Equalizer EP, 1996; SR-21150; DJ Equalizer; Sounds of Silence (Box 26)
          Catalog # ICR 002; A-side Matrix # ICR-002 SIDE THIS
        - DJ Fixx - The fixx EP, 2001; SR-25063; DJ Fixx (Box 26)
          Catalog # FW003; A-side Matrix # AE 21233/A
          Funk Wax
          Longwood, Florida
        - DJ Gumbee - Inside the night; Future retro, 2000; SR-21151; DJ Gumbee (Box 26)
          Catalog # Zone 040; A-side Matrix # MCR-RCE ZONE-040 A
        - DJ Gumbee - Can't get enuff, 2001; SR-21152; DJ Gumbee (Box 26)
          Catalog # Zone 046; A-side Matrix # MCR-RCE ZONE-046 A
        - DJ Ice - Baltimore Breakbeats Presents DJ Ice, 2002; SR-21153; DJ Ice (Box 26)
          Catalog # CBICE/01; A-side Matrix # 0204X10 A
          Club Beats Records
        - DJ Icey - Chain reaction; Low tide, 2000; SR-21154; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21155. Different discs.
          Catalog # Zone 038; A-side Matrix # ZONE 038A
        - City-Wide Allstars - Division 2, 2001; SR-21155; City-Wide Allstars (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21154. Different discs.
        - DJ Icey - You got to know, SR-21156; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21157. Different discs. Test pressing
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # OB-001-A1
        - Valley of the Big Bass and Big Bass Drum - Signal 2; Double down, 1997; SR-21157; Valley of the Big Bass and Big Bass Drum; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21156. Different discs.
          Catalog # TREE #8; A-side Matrix # tree008/9700x22 A
        - DJ Icey - The one; Message from space, 2000; SR-21158; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          Catalog # Zone 041; A-side Matrix # ZONE-041-A
        - DJ Icey - Say what ya'll, 1997; SR-21159; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          Catalog # Zone 023; A-side Matrix # ZONE-28 A
        - DJ Baby Anne - She said (City-Wide Allstars remix); Transmitter: on, 2002; SR-21160; DJ Baby Anne; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          Catalog # Zone 053; A-side Matrix # ZONE-053 A
        - DJ Icey - Vocodor bass; Department 3, 1998; SR-21161; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21162. Different discs.
          Catalog # Zone 028; A-side Matrix # ZONE-028 A
        - Lexy & K-Paul - You're the one, 2000; SR-21162; Lexy & K-Paul (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21161. Different discs.
          Catalog # 74321 83260 1; A-side Matrix # B043216-01 A1 HL
          Low Spirit Recordings
          Berlin, Germany
        - DJ Icey - Pump the bass (Peace to all the DJs); It ain't hard to tell, 1996; SR-25073; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          Different jacket
          Catalog # Tree 007; A-side Matrix # TREE 007-A
        - DJ Icey - Beats & tracks volume 11, 1999; SR-25074; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-25075. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # ECB 011; A-side Matrix # ECB-011-A
          ECB Records
        - DJ Icey - Beats & tracks volume 11, 1999; SR-25075; DJ Icey (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-25074. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Jonny Blaze - Club tracks Vol. 1, 2004; SR-21163; DJ Jonny Blaze (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21164. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # B1R-0001; A-side Matrix # B1R 0001-A
          Blaze One Records
        - DJ Jonny Blaze - Club tracks Vol. 1, 2004; SR-21164; DJ Jonny Blaze (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21163. Multiple copies.
        - DJ Juanito - Ain't no party like a Latin party, 1996; SR-21165; DJ Juanito; Bomba Factory (Box 26)
          Catalog # JCL-0083; A-side Matrix # L-47563-X JCL-0083-B
          Groove Nation Records
        - DJ Kool - The music ain't loud enuff, 1990; SR-21166; DJ Kool (Box 26)
          Catalog # SOH 7000; A-side Matrix # CFM/SOH-7000-A-C1
          S.O.H. Distributors Network
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - DJ Kool - Let me clear my throat, 1996; SR-21167; DJ Kool (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21168. 2 copies.
          Catalog # CLR 5218; A-side Matrix # CLR-5218-1A F/W RCE
          CLR
        - DJ Kool - Let me clear my throat, 1996; SR-21168; DJ Kool (Box 26)
          In same jacket as # SR-21167. 2 copies.
        - DJ LBR - Let me clear my funk; NY make some noise, 2002; SR-21169; DJ LBR (Box 27)
          Catalog # XL-109; A-side Matrix # XL-109 A
          Platinum Party Breaks
        - DJ Marquis - What'cha come to do?, 1995; SR-21170; DJ Marquis; Delawyse; Loco (Box 27)
          Catalog # NF3667; A-side Matrix # NF-3667A-REI
          Nu Flava Records
        - DJ Marquis - What'cha come to do?, 1995; SR-21171; DJ Marquis; Delawyse; Loco (Box 27)
        - DJ Mixtc - Something like this, 1997; SR-21172; DJ Mixtc (Box 27)
          Catalog # PG 05; A-side Matrix # PG 05-A XR+1D
          Platinum Groove Entertainment
          Palm Beach, Florida
        - DJ Omega - Shake that thang remixes, 1999; SR-21174; DJ Omega (Box 27)
          Catalog # DB-020; A-side Matrix # DB019-A DJ OMEGA-SHAKE THAT THANG-REMIXES NSC
          Databass Records
          Sterling Heights, Michigan
        - DJ Oscure - DMT3 presents LABA, 2002; SR-21175; DJ Oscure; Commander of Bass; Rocrite (Box 27)
          Catalog # CML-719; A-side Matrix # CML-719-A S-50358
          DMT3
        - DJ Patrick - Klap yo hand; Do dat dance; Do dat beat, 2003; SR-25064; DJ Patrick (Box 27)
          Catalog # QR-035; A-side Matrix # L-12023-A QR-035A
          Quiet Records
        - DJ Phlav - Old school phlava, 2001; SR-21176; DJ Phlav (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21177. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BDS-899; A-side Matrix # BDS-899-A-RE-1 EUROPADISK OMM NY USA 51703 DON CROSSINGER
          Buds Distribution
        - DJ Phlav - Old school phlava, 2001; SR-21177; DJ Phlav (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21176. 2 copies.
        - DJ Quik - Quik is the name, 1991; SR-21178; DJ Quik (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21179. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PRO-1402A; A-side Matrix # PRO-1402-A-REI 1-1
          Profile Records
        - DJ Quik - Quik is the name, 1991; SR-21179; DJ Quik (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21178. 2 copies.
        - DJ Rated R - The journey; Wired, 2002; SR-21180; DJ Rated R (Box 27)
          Catalog # B-008; A-side Matrix # 6614-B008-1 (A) S-49394
          BreakLogix
        - DJ Red Alert - Hip hop on wax volume 2, 1984; SR-25001; DJ Red Alert (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-25002. 2 copies.
          Catalog # VTIS-003; A-side Matrix # VTIS-003
          Vintertainment
        - DJ Red Alert - Hip hop on wax volume 2, 1984; SR-25002; DJ Red Alert (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-25001. 2 copies.
        - DJ Rod Lee - Froot loop project, 1998; SR-25065; DJ Rod Lee; Lee, Rod (Box 27)
          Catalog # CBR-CK/013; A-side Matrix # 0202X16-A
        - DJ Sebel - The Berlin connection, 1996; SR-21181; DJ Sebel (Box 27)
          Catalog # RUDEAD 008; A-side Matrix # RUDEAD 8A-1 MUSIC HOUSE
          Rude & Deadly Records
        - DJ Self - Don't stop, 2001; SR-21182; DJ Self (Box 27)
          Catalog # R2MPR-600; A-side Matrix # R2MPR600 A 1
          Phusion Records
          Mesquite, Texas
        - DJ Silver - Don't panic! (disc one), 1999; SR-21183; DJ Silver (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21184. Double album.
          Catalog # LSM001; A-side Matrix # LSM001-A-RE
          Liquid Sky
        - DJ Silver - Don't panic! (disc two), 1999; SR-21184; DJ Silver (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21183. Double album.
          Catalog # LSM001; A-side Matrix # LSM001-C
        - DJ Sir Charles - Summertime thong!, 2000; SR-21185; DJ Sir Charles (Box 27)
          Catalog # SWI-022; A-side Matrix # MB SWI-022 A
          Swirl Records
        - DJ Sir RJ - One for the treble what, 2001; SR-21186; DJ Sir RJ (Box 27)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # L-12535M-A
          Afterdark Fla-va Party Records
          Richmond, Virginia
        - DJ Soul Slinger - M.A.U. #1, 1999; SR-21187; DJ Soul Slinger (Box 27)
          Catalog # JSK143; A-side Matrix # JSK-143A-1A RJ
          Jungle Sky
        - DJ Swamp - Never is now (disc one), 2001; SR-21188; DJ Swamp (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21189. Double album.
          Catalog # LAK-33685-1; A-side Matrix # LAK-33685-1-A
          Lakeshore Records
        - DJ Swamp - Never is now (disc two), 2001; SR-21189; DJ Swamp (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21188. Double album.
          Catalog # LAK-33685-1; A-side Matrix # LAK-33685-1-C
        - DJ Taz - Chant 4 the crowd, 1997; SR-21190; DJ Taz (Box 27)
          Catalog # SPRO 30198; A-side Matrix # SPRO 30198 S-36385
          Priority Records
        - DJ Volume - Jump; Juice it (remix), 2002; SR-21195; DJ Volume (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21196. 2 copies.
          Catalog # KAL-037; A-side Matrix # KAL037 A
          Kaleidoscope
          Tampa, Florida
        - DJ Volume - Jump; Juice it (remix), 2002; SR-21196; DJ Volume (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-22195. 2 copies.
        - DJ Wally - Join us or die; Strap up, 1999; SR-21197; DJ Wally (Box 27)
          Catalog # JSK145; A-side Matrix # JSK 145 A
        - DJ Wally - The stoned ranger rydes again, 1999; SR-21198; DJ Wally (Box 27)
          Catalog # HOE131; A-side Matrix # HOE-131A- 1A RJ
          Home Entertainment
        - DJ Wally - The stoned ranger rydes again, 1999; SR-21199; DJ Wally (Box 27)
          Catalog # HOE132; A-side Matrix # HOE-132A- 1A RJ
        - DJ Wild - Ear wax vol. 2, 2001; SR-25066; DJ Wild (Box 27)
          Catalog # EW-200; A-side Matrix # EW-200 A1
          R2M
        - Djam & Fam - Raï derli, 1997; SR-21200; Djam & Fam (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21201. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0630-16751-0; A-side Matrix # WMME Alsdorf 063 016751-0-A
          Wea Music
        - Djam & Fam - Raï derli, 1997; SR-21201; Djam & Fam (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21200. 2 copies.
        - Do It Real - Keep on movin', 1997; SR-21202; Do It Real (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21203. 2 copies. Test Pressing
          Catalog # FGR9502-1; A-side Matrix # FGR 9502-A
          Feelin' Groovy Records
          Elmhurst, Illinois
        - Do It Real - Keep on movin', 1997; SR-21203; Do It Real (Box 27)
          In same jacket as # SR-21202. 2 copies. Test Pressing
          Catalog # FGR9502-1; A-side Matrix # FGR 9502-B
        - Dockett, Jimmy - Beauty & soul, 1976; SR-21204; Dockett, Jimmy (Box 27)
          Catalog # IM-302; A-side Matrix # IM302A- Z-
          Image Records
        - Dodson, Venus - Night rider, 1979; SR-21205; Dodson, Venus (Box 27)
          Catalog # RFC 3348; A-side Matrix # RFC-1-3348
        - Dodson, Venus - Night rider; Where are we headed, 1979; SR-21206; Dodson, Venus (Box 27)
          Catalog # RCSD 8824; A-side Matrix # RCSD-8824-WNY-1841-S-M1 24283
        - Dolby, Thomas - Europa and the pirate twins, 1981; SR-21207; Dolby, Thomas (Box 27)
          Factory Sample
          Catalog # 12R6051; A-side Matrix # 12R 6051 B-1U 13
          EMI
        - Dolby, Thomas - The flat Earth, 1984; SR-21208; Dolby, Thomas (Box 27)